Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
So he's...
the Emperor!
It really is a kid.
So the announcements were just him acting...
It's more mysterious and
exciting that way, isn't it?
So tell me, was it fun?
Shut up!
Do you realize how many people—
You okay, Sane?!
C'mon, Dad.
I went out of my way to make
this precious time for us.
Calm down. Let's have a nice,
calm heart-to-heart... Dad.
Try imagining my life.
A nauseating nightmare of a bunch
of sleazy, power-hungry strangers
toying around with your body,
mind, and life,
only to be put on a pedestal
and showered with attention
the second you pull the golden ticket.
No one treated me like a person.
That's why I killed them:
to show them I have my own will, too.
And that's when I found out...
that someone had a trump card against me: the Right of Parental authority.
But I was happy.
Happy to know that someone out there
was destined to be my parent.
If my parent were a person, that
would make me a person too, right?
Stay cool, Saneatsu!
The Emperor made you forfeit
your Parental Authority.
Even if he's telling the truth,
it's irrelevant at this point!
Sure, I guess.
I really am glad to meet you, but...
I have total command with Tasuketsu.
And it's the best feeling in the world.
If I can just recover every Right,
I can even realize my own perfect world.
I'm going to make this place my Utopia!
Do you know where the Rights came from?
Of course I do.
They're a collection of human greed that
manifested over the long course of history
until a certain event caused them
to materialize into our world.
Crazy, isn't it? That's what
this world is coming to.
Did you find that out using
some other Right you recovered?
I don't know too much beyond that.
Maybe if there were a God or his subjects
that existed, we could ask them.
God's... subjects...
Anyway, what are you guys
planning to do here?
You've already forfeited
your Parental Authority.
And my defenses are perfect.
I hate to say it, but you have no chance.
We know your only way of killing people
is through Tasuketsu...
Fine, then how about this?
We'll take one more tally right now, and
in turn, I'll call that the end of Tasuketsu.
I can't submit questions myself.
And you've killed all the puppets
in charge of my library...
so I'll have you delegate the exercising power
of the Questionnaire Right over to me.
I'm now exercising my Negotiation Right.
You'll take tally here and now, or you'll
leave and continue Tasuketsu as before.
Choose.
I have one condition.
What's that?
Limit the scope of Tasuketsu
to those here right now.
You mean so you don't involve
the others? That's fine.
Then I agree to your proposal...
to take the final tally.
Since you're a group and all, don't
you have something I can call you?
Like a team name?
I knew it!
It's Team Saneatsu.
Cool, let me check with the other three.
Answer me. Are you all Team Saneatsu?
Yeah.
I am.
Me too.
Negotiation complete.
Hey, Saneatsu...
this is like that one time. Remember?
Yeah, you mean that night? Of course I do.
We promised to defeat the Emperor.
Thanks to that promise,
we have nothing to fear.
Can we join you guys?
Thanks. We're in this together.
We always were... and always will be.
It's time. We will now
begin tallying the majority.
I reject.
A question for those within the 210th floor of the Emperor's tower.
Are you part of Team Saneatsu?
Damn it!
We've passed midnight.
Idiots! Death of negotiating partners
nullifies agreements!
That's the power of the
Prime Right of Negotiation!
Complete and total victory!
You greedy, rotten humans don't deserve
to live, even if you begged for forgiveness!
The Right of Parental Authority
and its owner are both gone!
I have nothing to fear now!
I'll kill off every human being,
recover every single Right,
and build a new, pure world free of greed!
I've finally made it!
My ideal world is almost—
Die
Wha—
What is this?!
Die
What's... happening?
H-How?
You were... dead...
This is the end, Emperor.
No...
Why... me? Why... do I have to... die?
Someone like... me... who's
endured... so much pain...
I could... build an... ideal... world...
As someone who was
in the same boat, I can tell...
What you're doing is repeating
the same nightmare.
Ryuta-kun... how ya doing? Ya okay?
Yeah. I'm fine now.
Looks like I was able to fuse
with the puppets, but...
it's taking a while to set in.
The plan was a success!
They did it?!
Like this, right?
Mm-yup...
Here's our ultimate plan.
There's no doubt the Emperor
will use Tasuketsu to kill us.
First off, I'm handing the Obedience
Right's envelopes to Gobo.
R-Right on.
Die
Inside are the words "Die" for 2, "Protect" for 3,
"Destroy" for 4, and "Love" for 5.
Protect
Destroy
Love
They're all simple commands.
Of these, the command to "die" should
be most useful in almost any situation.
Die
We'll use this to defeat the Emperor.
You sure it'll work?
To make sure it does,
we'll have to take the highest likelihood
of success, regardless of the risks.
We'll display this command remotely
using Gobo's Presentation Right.
Of course! That should... wait, but...
The red laptop will be recovered tonight.
Which means the Emperor will
have it when we take our shot.
Two left
You are currently looking at this screen
Regardless of whether we see it or not,
One left
Japanese citizens living
in Tokyo Prefecture
Male or female
Tasuketsu may require displaying
information on a screen.
As a result of Tasuketsu, I'm...
Alive or Dead
You are currently looking
at this screen in Tokyo Prefecture.
Prime Rights: 12 left
Rights: 45 left
40 years of age
Under or Over
1,081,990 people left
The Emperor can't submit
questions themselves.
They probably can't impose
their will on Tasuketsu.
So that'll be our play.
We'll submit the question for them.
A question the Emperor most desires...
Meaning... our annihilation.
The Emperor has the power
to nullify submissions.
And if they do, it'll be the usual
Tasuketsu the next day.
We can't let that happen.
Which is why we have to
all die through Tasuketsu.
This is necessary for the plan to work.
So we'll decide on a team name.
The Emperor will conduct Tasuketsu subjecting
team members to "yes" or "no" questions.
To make sure the others aren't included,
we'll separate into two teams starting today.
Those that will invade the Emperor's
tower are Team Saneatsu.
The rest will all be under Team Yagihashi.
I bet the Emperor will check each
person's team to make sure we all die.
Omi has the Rejection Right,
so he can survive by rejecting tally.
That's perfect. Your hands in your pocket.
Pretend you're dead in that exact position.
And Ryuta, I want you to survive by fusing
yourself with the cells of puppets.
Can you do that?
Y-Yeah...
After the Emperor takes tally,
act like you're desperate
and turn the laptop screen
towards the Emperor.
With the screen facing the Emperor,
Omi will send a message on his
cellphone hidden in his pocket.
Back at headquarters,
Gobo will keep an eye on Omi's cellphone
screen using his Presentation Right.
When Omi's message comes through,
Gobo will display command number 2
to the Emperor's laptop.
No matter what, don't look at it yourself.
Open the envelope, unfold the note,
and display its words on the laptop
Ryuta touches tonight.
Omi, give the final update
on whether the plan worked.
Wait, but...
Then you're saying...
I...
will die.
He was right about
how everything would unfold.
Mm-yup... Saneatsu was my hero.
Even though no one will know,
he saved humanity.
Yeah.
He always used to call me his hero,
but turns out he's my hero now.
Man...
They're still right here, but...
Mm-yup...
It's just for now.
Finally... the moment I've been waiting for!
Neither Sanetomo's son nor the Emperor
were a match for me!
Everything went according to plan!
I've inerited the Recovery Right!
Now all I need to do is wait two days
to recover the Rights scattered
from the Emperor's death!
I'm the true ruler!
I've been waiting for this moment, Mido.
Tough luck for you!
Iruga?!
You must have not noticed me hiding
behind you through space division!
I would have killed you earlier,
but isn't it more pathetic if I do it
during this victory speech of yours?
What are you doing here?
Teppei-chan's justice came through.
I did promise Narita-chan, after all.
Iruga!
"According to plan"? I'm afraid not!
Narita-chan won this match.
Divide to maximum limit.
Bye bye, Mido.
Welp. Now what...
I guess as long as I have this, I'm good.
What's wrong, Gobo?
I get you're happy, but...
It's nothing!
Now, I've got one more big job to finish!
Let's do this, for real!
Hey, you sure Saneatsu and Saaya escaped?
I told you, they escaped!
We'll meet them again!
It's almost time.
As of this moment,
Tasuketsu has concluded.
It's really over.
Yeah...
As of this moment, Tasuketsu has concluded.
But I wish I could have...
seen the light at the end
of the tunnel together, Sane.
June 13th. Tasuketsu came to a close.
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Driving without a license? What an outlaw.
Gimme a break. I'm wearing a seat belt.
That's not my point.
What happens if you're in an accident?
We've got the Evasion Right.
Hey!
So where are we headed again?
To my hometown, Aomori.
The Emperor mentioned "God's subjects"...
It's the same kanji as my name.
Best to check it out.
Besides, maybe we can channel Sane
if we train as one of their mediums!
Please tell me you're kidding
with that spiritual woo-woo.
The Rights existed, so
why couldn't that be true too?
I don't expect it to come true,
but it's the hope that matters.
Isn't that what dreams are for?
And there's mountains and oceans
in the countryside.
Unlike Tokyo, we could support ourselves.
Wow, you're one grounded guy.
Just what I'd expect from
the man who saved my life!
Or should I say... my future husband!
I want a girl whose more
of the "cute" type...
Nah, you can't stick two "cute"
types together or they'll die off.
What kind of logic is that?!
Oh well, take me anywhere you like.
I'll be your guardian angel.
All right! Let's get going!
Hey, stop! Lemme off!
I reject!
Hey! No fair!
Damn, it's like a ghost town.
Jeez, these have all gone bad too.
Must be from that week or so
when the power was out.
You mean when Tasuketsu ended?
Hey, didn't Shige live around here?
Um... yeah. But he's dead, remember?
Right, but his house ran
completely on electricity.
With power and water, we can...
Take a shower!
It's still intact!
I heard the riots got real bad around here.
I even heard there were flying monsters.
Hey! What are you doing at Shige's place?!
Oh, are you... acquaintances?
Ahh, I'm s-sorry...
You're lucky, kid.
I don't usually do this,
but I'll let you choose.
Get beat to death now or become my servant.
I-I'll become your servant!
Please don't kill me!
Ha! Sounds like you'd be perfect for the job!
I-I just used the restroom!
I didn't even take the canned food
in the kitchen, I swear!
Hey, how many cans were there?
Um... Maybe two full boxes?
Nice! All right then...
Let's have some dinner before we shower!
Would you look at that.
New apartments have such sturdy doors.
You should've had your guard up when
you noticed the security system was down.
I'm Raion Ouno, and I love lying.
Why you...
Propane gas sure is dangerous.
This place runs on electricity! You did that!
I lied about not stealing canned food too.
I get it... so you must
enjoy killing for sport too...
"Enjoy"? You mean this
is just play time for you?
I have way better survival
skills than you guys.
You little—
You guys are the kind that
get caught... by a liar like me.
Here's another lie.
Besides, how do you not
notice a trap like this?
Speaking of lies... it's about time.
Good evening.
This is your
Emperor.
Today's results
are as follows.
Today's execution has been determined to be Tamataro Yamada
(age 33), who killed three people in Meguro Ward. Goodbye.
Please bear in mind to refrain from evil,
and work to live as long as possible.
Even with the end of Tasuketsu,
the executions won't stop.
Please bear in mind to refrain from evil,
and work to live as long as possible.
You just have to stay out of trouble, I think.
There's something off about these...
These messages reek of lies.
All right, message delivered!
Hey, Nishime! Tea, please!
Come on, again?
And could you cut it out with
that name? "Nishime" is food.
Shuji Nihonyanagi
Whaddaya mean?
Your name is Shuji Nihonyanagi,
so it's "ni" and "shi" paired with "me"!
And you're talking to a guy
people call "Gobo"!
Burdock root and stewed vegetables
make a good pair.
Says who?
Oh, you all done with the stream?
Hey, how did the town look?
Lots of weird stuff, but
nothing out of the ordinary.
Shinozaki-san is patrolling
the area right now.
Hey, Emperor in disguise,
are you eating out of hours again?
I'm the Emperor for real now though.
Oh, are you? Then we need to kill you off.
Never mind... I was just kidding.
Humanity was left with
one million people in Tokyo.
Are we going extinct or
will we reconstruct society?
The only people who know
about Saneatsu and Saaya's deaths
are me, Team Saneatsu, and Rika Suzuki.
The rest of the group
thinks they're in hiding
because of conditions
from the Negotiation Right.
And there's three others whose
whereabouts are unknown...
Ren Iruga said he killed off Mido,
but he's disappeared since.
There's only two left of the four volunteers.
Hikari and Nishime are working
with me as my assistants.
He told us to leave their bodies here...
We could've at least saved Saaya...
That's not true.
Defeating the Emperor was
the end for the both of them...
They were sincere like that.
Eren, it's time to deliver another message.
Oh, right!
Good evening. This is your Emperor.
Today's results are as follows.
Fictional people and incidents,
along with the memories of Tasuketsu...
These three elements should ensure
that people keep the peace!
Gobo...
Don't worry, no one will notice
the Emperor's a fake!
When did the Emperor change?
I better go meet them.
The Emperor will now become the Queen.
And the Queen...
Closing
shall grant your wishes.